>> Brian Holt: Hoks 是 React 的真正新功能。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Hooks is
a really new feature to React.
如果你在你听说过的泰维特斯球上
It's probably something that if you're
on the Twitterspheres that you've heard
啊，对吧 ?
of, right?
这可能是在 11 月，当他们宣布的时候。
And this got introduced maybe about,
November is when they announced it.
它已经被卷走了
And it's been rolling out.
因此，它现在一般都可以作为第 16.8 号法案使用。
And so now it's generally
available as of React 16.8.
所以我现在要告诉你的第一件事是，这完全是选择性的。
So the first thing I'm gonna tell you
right now is, that's totally optional.
你现在不用胡克丝了
You do not have to use Hooks right now.
但是我要先给你教给他们，
But I am going to teach them to you first,
因为我觉得他们是想写 React 组件的更容易的方法
because I think they're an easier way to
think about writing React components.
然后我们也要去另一种语法，就是类语法，
And then we're also going to the other
syntax as well which is class syntax,
你得知道这俩人的事好吗
cuz you need to know both of them, okay?
>> Brian Holt: 对于观看视频的人，如果您正在观看
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: For those of you that
are watching the video, if you're watching
这只是为了学胡克丝这里有一个叫 Hook in Depth的章节
this just to learn Hooks, there is
a section here called Hooks in Depth.
这也许是个跳跳跳伞的好东西对吧
It's probably a good sport to jump in,
right?
因为那部分完全孤立于其他的
Because that section is totally
isolated from the other ones and
它会穿过所有钩子
it goes over all of the hooks.
>> 扬声器 2: 将在中间重定向课程中。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That will be in
the Intermediate React course.
>> Brian Holt: 是，将在中间 React 课程中。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yes, that will be
in the Intermediate React course.
我认为这是 " 中级反应 " 课程的第一部分。
I think it is the first section
of the Intermediate React course.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，但你也可以从这里开始。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, but
you could also start from here as well.
所以，让我们来谈谈钩子会为我们做些什么。
So, let's talk about what hooks do for us.
>> Brian Holt: 让我们回到我们的代码，让我们在这里做一个新的组件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's go back to our
code, let's make a new component here.
我们会叫它 SearchParams.js
And we're gonna call it SearchParams.js.
也会在源目录里
It's gonna be inside
the source directory as well.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将从 "反应"中导入 React 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here we're going
to import React from 'react'.
Say const SearchParams 将等于一个箭头函数。
Say const SearchParams is gonna
be equal to an arrow function.
> > Brian Holt: 我要给它点位置。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm gonna
give it some location.
> > Brian Holt: 这样做会像西雅图和 WA一样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is gonna
be something like Seattle, WA.
>> Brian Holt: 确保该位置是美国的位置。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sure that
this is an American location.
我们将使用的 API 仅限于美国。
The API that we're gonna be
using is limited to the US.
事实上，我现在只限制了西雅图和旧金山的空气污染指数。
And actually I've limited the API to just
Seattle and San Fransisco right now.
所以也许选择其中之一。
So maybe choose one of those.
> > Brian Holt: 我会在这里解释一下为什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
I'll explain why here in a second.
因此，请在此处制作一个 div >> Brian Holt: And
So make a div here
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
所以我还没跟你解释
so one thing I haven't explained to you so
这个挺重要的，我想给这个名字，对吧 ?
far that is pretty important is I
wanna give this a class name, right?
通常，我只说类等于搜索 - params，就像这样。
So typically, I'll just say class
equals search-params, like this.
但通知会说我不知道课是什么
But notice it's gonna say,
I don't know what class is.
使用类时存在问题。
There's problem with using class.
问题是，类是 JavaScript 中的保留字。
And the issue is that class is
a reserved word in JavaScript.
所以如果我说 " 宠物宠物 " 之类的话
So if I say something like class Pet or
something like that.
此处的类在 JavaScript 中有一个含义，对吧 ?
Class here has a meaning in JavaScript,
right?
就像我不能说的， const class = blah，
Just like I can't say, const class = blah,
因为这是个保留字对吧
is because this is a reserved word, right?
意外关键字表示您不能将其用作变量名，对吗 ?
Unexpected keyword means it's a word that
you cannot use as a variable name, right?
我也不能叫这叫康斯特的
Same thing,
I can't have this called const,
我不能让这个叫的对吧
I can't have this called let, right?
类是其中的另一个。
Class is another one of those.
那么我们如何使用 JSX来解决这一问题 ?
So how do we get around that with JSX?
那么，我们使用 JavaScript API 的名称，该名称是 className。
Well, we use the name of
the JavaScript API, which is a className.
他们没有发明这种方法，但这不是一种 " 重新发明 " 的限制。
They didn't invent this, but this was
not a limitation that React invented.
实际上，它也是 DOM API 的名称，所以
And actually,
it's the name of the DOM API as well, so
也符合 DOM 的要求
it's consistent with
what the DOM calls it.
这就是为什么这是 className 而不是只是类，对吧 ?
So that's why this is className
instead of just class, right?
我知道人们觉得这很烦人，但它就是这样。
I understand that people find that
annoying, but it is what it is.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我们要在里面放一个表格。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
inside of that we're gonna put a form.
在里面我们要有个标签和同样的东西在这里对吧
Inside of that we're gonna have a label
and same thing here with for, right?
这是另一个保留字，就像在循环中，对吧 ?
For is another reserve word,
as in for loop, right?
所以 htmlFor
So htmlFor.
>> Brian Holt: 这是针对位置的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
this is for the location.
>> Brian Holt: 在此范围内，我希望为其提供输入
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Inside of that,
I want to give it location with an input
>> Brian Holt: Id = "location"。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Id = "location".
位置 =，然后我们把花括号放在这里
Location =, and
then we're gonna put curly braces here
因为我们想把这里放在这里
because we want this location
here to be put there.
抱歉这不是地点这将是有价值的
Sorry, and this isn't gonna be location,
this is gonna be value.
值 = 。
Value = .
>> Brian Holt: And 占位符 = "Location"。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
placeholder = "Location".
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And underneath that
we're gonna have outside of that,
在 " 表单 " 按钮的内部， " 提交" ，就像这样。
inside of the Form button,
Submit, like that.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，请在此处汲取经验，导出缺省值。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
lesson down here, export default.
>> Brian Holt: SearchParams。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: SearchParams.
>> Brian Holt: 最后一行。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Last line there.
> > Brian Holt: 我们制作了这个新组件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we've made this new component,
就会像个搜索箱一样
that's gonna be a little like search box.
所以我们可以搜索宠物的不同方面，对，
So we can search for
various different facets of pets, right,
针对 Pet Finder API。
against the Pet Finder API.
它有一个内部有一个形式的 div 。
And it has a div with a form inside of it.
我们有一个有标签的输入。
And we have a input with a label for it.
有些人也许会觉得这有点奇怪
Some of you might find this like
a little strange way to nest it.
这是你能做的
This is one way that you can do
标签中输入的标签。
labels that you put the input
inside of the label.
还有其他的方法可以做到
There's other ways of doing it as well.
但最终，这对辅助功能是很有利的。
But in the end,
it's just good for accessibility.
如果有人点击了它的位置
So that if someone clicks
on the location that it
输入正确的输入，对吗 ?
highlights the correct input, right?
这就是我们要做的
That's ultimately what
we're going here for.
它会有西雅图的价值，华盛顿，对吧 ?
And it's gonna have a value of Seattle,
Washington, right?
所以，让我们先去了解 app.js。
So let's go ahead and
go render that out to app.js.
而不是 app.js， >> Brian Holt: 确保获取
So instead of app.js,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sure you get
啊，这个对。
this right.
我们可以删除所有评论过的东西
Yep, we can delete all this
stuff that we commented out.
> > Brian Holt: 在此，我们不再从 Pet 导入。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here,
we're not gonna import from Pet anymore.
我们现在不能用宠物了
We cannot use Pet right now.
我们会说，从 ./SearchParams 导入 SearchParams 。
We'll say,
import SearchParams from ./SearchParams.
> > Brian Holt: 我们将删除所有这些宠物，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're going to
delete all these pets, and
就像这样把 SearchParams 放了
just put SearchParams like that.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，再一次打开 SearchParams ，以防您遗漏了什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, open SearchParams one
more time, in case you missed something.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我现在需要确保服务器正在运行。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now I need to make
sure that my server is running.
我的仍在运行，但确保您的正在运行。
Mine is still running, but
make sure yours is running.
然后确保在此处打开 localhost 1234 。
And then make sure you
open localhost 1234 here.
我有点舞跳但没明确提到
Something I kind of danced around but
didn't explicitly mention was that.
你不能做我之前给你展示的那种文件
You can't do that file open thing
that I was showing you before,
不能再工作了
that no longer works.
你得把这个包裹在包裹里的服务器上
You have to be loading this
off of Parcel's server, right?
这就是为什么必须关闭 localhost: 1234。
Which is why you have to open
it off of the localhost: 1234.
> > Brian Holt: 所以我们要重新打开它，我在这里。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So we're gonna open
that again, which I have up here.
你可以看到我在西雅图有个地方
And you can see,
I have a location here, with Seattle,
华盛顿有个 " 提交 " 的按钮对吧
Washington, with the Submit button there,
right?